Viewers, I mean those under the influence of my voice, I will put them as I am sent.
This is not mine - the word.
The Book of Psalms 9:10 said that because I know His name, I will put my trust in Him.
Tell your neighbour, "I know His name; I will put my trust in Him".
His name is Jesus Christ.
There is a wonderful name Jesus
There is no other name I know
As you seek God, be fulfilled.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Find fulfillment as you seek God, in Jesus' name.
There is a wonderful name Jesus
There is no other name I know
Find fulfillment as you seek Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
As you seek Him, find fulfillment, in the name of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to confess His Word over your situation.
Confess His Word over your situation.
Let the weak say, "I am strong".
Let the poor say, "I am blessed".
Let the sick say, " I am healed".
Let the oppressed say, "I am delivered".
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
I command deliverance on you, in the name of Jesus!
I command blessing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Open your lips and begin to confess His Word over your situation.
When I am weak, I am strong.
When I am poor, I am blessed.
When I am oppressed, I am set free.
Confess His Word.
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray.
Listen to His Word.
His Word says, "When I am poor, I am blessed. When I am sick, I am healed.
When I am oppressed, I am set free. When I am weak, I am strong".
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever pain or affliction is in your system, be healed!
Be healed!
Wherever in your organs, blood, fluids, tendons, liver or kidneys,
wherever affliction is - be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, open your lips and begin to confess His Word over your situation.
When I am weak, then I am strong.
When I am poor, then I am blessed.
When I am oppressed, then I am set free.
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
I command healing on your system, in the name of Jesus!
I command healing in your liver!
Every part of your system, be healed!
Be delivered!
Be set free!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Listen.
Are you one of those who attend the church where others sense God's presence
and you are detached and numb?
Whatever wall that separates you and God - be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever hindrance between you and God - be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Let there be a relationship.
Let the relationship between you and God be re-established!
Relationship between you and God be re-established!
Be re-established, in Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, give thanks to God for taking you out - out of the pain, hardship, poverty and affliction.
Give thanks to God!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray!
As you know Jesus' name, be set on high!
Be set free, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
We say, "In Jesus' name".
But today, as you know the name Jesus, be set on high!
Be lifted up!
Be delivered!
Be healed!
Be set free, in the name of Jesus!
I will not leave you until I hear "Alright!"
We are going somewhere.
Tell yourself, "Jesus loves me. That is why I trust in Him".
You devil, I want to give you a !red card'!
I command you to remove your hand from my people!
Remove your hand I say, in Jesus' name!
That is 'red card'!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name